

# Matthew Rosenfeld, Associate Technologist

#### **Experience Summary**

Mr. Rosenfeld is a recent college graduate with a background in the areas of software development and engineering and experience in information technology development. Holding an BS in Electrical Engineering and minors in Computer Science and Music Performance, his well-rounded educational background enables him to be a quick learner and eagerly recognize, understand and confront a variety of different types of challenges he or his team may face.

### Relevant Accomplishments/Skills

- Communication: A technical education coupled with a variety of undergraduate leadership roles prepares him for conveying complex technical ideas in a way that any type of shareholder could understand and appreciate.
- Technical: His minor in computer science covered everything a bachelor's degree would have apart from a few upper level electives. This education prepares him to take on a variety of unique technical challenges.

### **Education, Certifications and Training**

- BS Electrical Engineering, University of Maryland, 2018
  - Minor: Computer Science

#### **Technical Skills**

Languages	Databases	Applications / Tools	Methodologies / Frameworks	Systems / Network Platforms
C#	SQL Server	MS Office Suite	Agile	Windows
ASP.NET	MySQL	JIRA	.NET Webforms	Ubuntu Linux
Python	Microsoft Access	Visual Studio	MEAN stack	
Javascript		VS Code		
NodeJS		Git		
С		Tortoise SVN		
Java				
SQL				

### **Professional Experience**

#### **Customer Value Partners**

August 2018-Present

## Associate Technologist, Department of Veterans Affairs (DVA)

- Responsible for fixing bugs and implementing new features in a timely manner at the clients' request
- Supports PM in communicating with client about issues and features and contributes ideas regarding how to solve problems the client faces

Key Technologies: ASP.NET - WebForms, C#, SQL Server, SVN, Jenkins, SSDT



### Developer, Internal Project

- Supported internal team on implementing a CKAN instance to serve as a CVP Internal Data Library
- Acted as system administrator and implement functional and aesthetic changes to site
- Conducted site demonstration to potential end users

Key Technologies: Python, Pyramids Web Framework, Jinja2 Templating, Linux

#### WD Lab Grown Diamonds

**January 2015–May 2018** 

#### **Operations Intern**

- Manage, maintain and build various aspects of the inventory tracking system
- Created version control system within Access for improved workflow and change documentation in a multi-developer environment
- Implement current programming skills while learning SQL and RDBMS concepts Key Technologies: Microsoft Access, Visual Basic for Applications, SQL

### Oak Ridge National Laboratory

**June 2016-August 2016** 

#### **Electrical Engineering Intern**

- Worked with a mentor to complete an engineering task related to Control Systems
- Completed a written 15 pg. report and poster on the research project
- Gave oral presentations to the research team and presented work at an intern research expo

Key Technologies: LabVIEW

# **Security Clearance**

• Public Trust, DVA (Active)

### **Work Experience Start**

Month	Year	Gap Years/Months
08	2018	0